A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia 1976-2003
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the President of the University of Virginia 1976-2003
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/1/2.041
These files constitute the major record series generated by the office of John Thomas Casteen, president of the University of Virginia since 1990. The records include ca. 21,600 items (54 Hollinger boxes, ca. 22.5 linear feet).
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access is prohibited for ten years from the date of creation unless special permission is granted by the President's Office. Under the terms of the Virginia Freedom of Information Act (Sec. 2.1-343 (4), the records of the president or other chief executive officer of any state-supported institution of higher education are exempt from the law's access provisions.
Additional access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.). Items identified as meeting these criteria have been placed in the restricted series of papers, but with its folder of origin noted in the guide.
Acquisition Information
These papers were transferred from the Office of the President, Madison Hall, University of Virginia through Jo Anne Birckhead on October 21, 2004.
Scope and Content
These files constitute the major record series generated by the office of John Thomas Casteen, president of the University of Virginia since 1990. The records, ca. 21,600 items (54 Hollinger boxes, ca. 22.5 linear feet), 1976-2003, (but chiefly dating from 2000-2003) consist mostly of correspondence, but also include reports, minutes, clippings, memoranda, and related papers concerning all areas of business of the president's office. These papers consist of office administrative files and miscellaneous topical files, mostly arranged alphabetically.
Arrangement
Both the series and file headings used by the president's office have been retained. Restricted material has been placed in its own series. There are four series: Series I) General Files (Boxes 1-35); Series II) Seldom Used Permanent Files (Boxes 35-47); Series III) Committee Files (Box 47); and Series IV) Restricted Files (Boxes 48-54).
Contents List
- Series I: General Files (Box 1-35)
  - "A-Al" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 1:1)
  - "Am" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 1:2)
  - "An-Ap" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 1:3)
  - "Ar-As" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 1:4)
  - "At-Ay" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 1:5)
  - African American Affairs - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 1:6)
  - Alumni Association - General and Board of Managers 2001 Dec.-2002 Jun. (Box-folder 2:1)
  - Alumni Association - General and Board of Managers 2001 Aug.-Nov. (Box-folder 2:2)
  - American Association of State Colleges & Universities 2001-2002 (Box-folder 2:3)
  - American Council on Education - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 2:4)
  - American Council on Education - "The Presidency" 2001-2002 (Box-folder 2:5)
  - Architecture - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 2:6)
  - Art - Bayly Art Museum 2001-2002 (Box-folder 3:1)
  - Art - Planning & Development for the Arts 2002 Feb. (Box-folder 3:2)
  - Arts & Sciences - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 3:3)
  - Association of Academic Health Centers 2001-2002 (Box-folder 3:4)
  - Association of American Colleges & Universities 2002 Apr. (Box-folder 3:5)
  - Association of American Colleges & Universities 2001 Oct.-2002 Mar. (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Association of American Universities - General 2002 May-Jun. (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Association of American Universities - General 2002 Mar.-Apr. (Box-folder 3:8)
  - Association of American Universities - General 2002 Apr. (Box-folder 4:1)
  - Association of American Universities - General 2002 Feb. (Box-folder 4:2)
  - Association of American Universities - General 2002 Feb. (Box-folder 4:3)
  - Association of American Universities - General 2002 Jan. (Box-folder 4:4)
  - Association of American Universities - General 2001 Nov.-Dec. (Box-folder 4:5)
  - Association of American Universities - General 2001 Oct. (Box-folder 4:6)
  - Association of American Universities - General 2001 Oct. (Box-folder 4:7)
  - Association of American Universities - General 2001 Oct. (Box-folder 5:1)
  - Association of American Universities - General 2001 Aug.-Sep. (Box-folder 5:2)
  - Association of American Universities - General 2001 Jul.-Aug. (Box-folder 5:3)
  - Association of Governing Boards 2001-2002 (Box-folder 5:4)
  - Athletics - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 5:5)
  - Athletics - Atlantic Coast Conference 2002 Feb.-Jul. (Box-folder 6:1)
  - Athletics - Atlantic Coast Conference 2001 Oct.-2002 Jan. (Box-folder 6:2)
  - Athletics - Atlantic Coast Conference 2001 Jun.-Sep. (Box-folder 6:3)
  - Athletics - NCAA 2002 Apr.-Jul. (Box-folder 6:4)
  - Athletics - NCAA 2002 Apr. (Box-folder 6:5)
  - Athletics - NCAA 2002 Jan.-Mar. (Box-folder 6:6)
  - Athletics - NCAA 2002 Jan. (Box-folder 7:1)
  - Athletics - NCAA 2002 Nov.-Dec. (Box-folder 7:2)
  - Athletics - NCAA 2001 Oct. (Box-folder 7:3)
  - Athletics - NCAA 2001 Sept.-Oct. (Box-folder 7:4)
  - Athletics - NCAA 2002 Jul.-Aug. (Box-folder 7:5)
  - Auditor - Internal - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 7:6)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts (State) 2001-2002 (Box-folder 8:1)
  - "Ba" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 8:2)
  - "Bd-Bl" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 8:3)
  - "Bo-Br" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 8:4)
  - "Bs-By" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 8:5)
  - Biology - General 2001 Sep. (Box-folder 8:6)
  - Business & Finance - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 8:7)
  - "Ca-Care" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 9:1)
  - "Cari-Cas" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 9:2)
  - "Cat-Chap" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 9:3)
  - "Char-Chr" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 9:4)
  - "Ci-Cl" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 9:5)
  - "Cob-Commo" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 10:1)
  - "Commu-Coo" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 10:2)
  - "Cop-Cu" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 10:3)
  - Career Services - General 2001 Jul. (Box-folder 10:4)
  - Carr's Hill - General 2002 Jun. (Box-folder 10:5)
  - Casteen, John T. III - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 10:6)
  - Cavalier Daily - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 10:7)
  - Charlottesville, City of - General 2002 Jun. (Box-folder 10:8)
  - Charlottesville, City of - PACC 2001-2002 (Box-folder 10:9)
  - Chemistry - General 2001 Nov. (Box-folder 10:10)
  - College Board - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 10:11)
  - Commerce School - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 10:12)
  - Commonwealth Public Broadcasting 2002 May-Jun. (Box-folder 11:1)
  - Commonwealth Public Broadcasting 2001 Jul.-2002 Apr. (Box-folder 11:2)
  - Community Relations - General 2002 Mar.-Jun. (Box-folder 11:3)
  - Condolences "A-F" 2001-2002 (Box-folder 11:4)
  - Condolences "G-W" 2001-2002 (Box-folder 11:5)
  - Congress - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 11:6)
  - Continuing & Professional Studies - General 2002 Jan.-Jul. (Box-folder 11:7)
  - Continuing & Professional Studies - General 2001 Jul.-Nov. (Box-folder 11:8)
  - Council for Higher Education Accreditation 2002 May-Jun. (Box-folder 12:1)
  - Council for Higher Education Accreditation 2002 Apr. (Box-folder 12:2)
  - Council for Higher Education Accreditation 2002 Apr. (Box-folder 12:3)
  - Council for Higher Education Accreditation 2002 Feb. (Box-folder 12:4)
  - Council for Higher Education Accreditation 2002 Jan. (Box-folder 12:5)
  - Council for Higher Education Accreditation 2001 Nov.-2002 Jan. (Box-folder 12:6)
  - Council for Higher Education Accreditation 2001 Jul.-Oct. (Box-folder 13:1)
  - Council of Presidents - General 2002 Jan.-Jun. (Box-folder 13:2)
  - Council of Presidents - General 2002 Jul.-Dec. (Box-folder 13:3)
  - Crotty, Gene - Jefferson's Western Travels 2001 Oct. (Box-folder 13:4)
  - "Da" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 13:5)
  - "De" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 13:6)
  - "Di" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 14:1)
  - "Do-Dy" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 14:2)
  - Darden School - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 14:3)
  - Development - General 2002 May-Jun. (Box-folder 14:4)
  - Development - General 2001 Nov-2002 Mar. (Box-folder 14:5)
  - Development - General 2001 Jul-Oct. (Box-folder 14:6)
  - Drama - General 2002 Jan.-Apr. (Box-folder 14:7)
  - "Ea-Em" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 14:8)
  - "En-Ex" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 15:1)
  - Economics - General 2002 Mar.-May (Box-folder 15:2)
  - Education School - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 15:3)
  - Education School 2002 Jan. (Folder 15:4)
  - Engineering & Applied Science - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 15:5)
  - English - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 15:6)
  - Enrollment - Enrollment Statistics 2001 Sep. (Box-folder 15:7)
  - Environmental Sciences - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 15:8)
  - Equal Opportunity Office - General 2001 Jul.-Sep. (Box-folder 15:9)
  - "Fa-Fe" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Folder 16:1)
  - "Fi-Fl" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 16:2)
  - "Fo-Fu" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 16:3)
  - Facilities Management - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 16:4)
  - Faculty - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 16:5)
  - Family Violence Prevention Fund - General 2001 Dec. (Box-folder 16:6)
  - Final Exercises 2001-2002 (Box-folder 16:7)
  - Financial Aid to Students Office - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 17:1)
  - Finance - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 17:2)
  - French Language & Literature - General 2001 Sep. (Box-folder 17:3)
  - "Ga-Ge" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 17:4)
  - "Gi-Go" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 17:5)
  - "Gr-Gw" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 17:6)
  - General Assembly - General 2002 Feb.-Jun. (Box-folder 17:7)
  - General Assembly - General 2001 Dec.-2002 Jan. (Box-folder 17:8)
  - General Assembly - General 2001 Nov. (Box-folder 18:1)
  - General Assembly - General 2001 Jul.-Sep. (Box-folder 18:2)
  - General Assembly - House Appropriations Committee 2001 Sep.-Nov. (Box-folder 18:3)
  - General Assembly - Senate Finance Committee 2001 Oct. (Box-folder 18:4)
  - General Council - General 2002 Jan.-Jun. (Box-folder 18:5)
  - General Services (State) - General 2001 Sep.-Dec. (Box-folder 18:6)
  - German Department - General 2001 Feb. (Box-folder 18:7)
  - Government & Foreign Affairs - General 2001 Aug.-Dec. (Box-folder 18:8)
  - Governmental Relations - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 18:9)
  - Governmental Relations - General 2001 Sep. (Box-folder 18:10)
  - Governor's Office 2001-2002 (Box-folder 18:11)
  - Governor's Office - Education 2002 Feb.-Jun. (Box-folder 18:12)
  - Governor's Office - Education 2001 Jul.-2002 Jan. (Box-folder 19:1)
  - Governor's Office - Finance 2001 Sep. (Box-folder 19:2)
  - Governor's Office - Technology 2001-2002 (Box-folder 19:3)
  - "Ha" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 19:4)
  - "He" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 19:5)
  - "Hi-Hop" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 19:6)
  - "Hor-Hy" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 19:7)
  - Honor System/Committee - General 2002 Jan.-May (Box-folder 19:8)
  - Housing - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 19:9)
  - Human Resources - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 19:10)
  - "IBM-Ins" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 19:11)
  - "Int-Is" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 20:1)
  - Information Technologies - General 2002 Jan.-Mar. (Box-folder 20:2)
  - Institutional Assessment & Studies - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 20:3)
  - International Students - General 2001 Nov. (Box-folder 20:4)
  - International Studies - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 20:5)
  - Invitations to Inaugurations "A-L" 2001-2002 (Box-folder 20:6)
  - Invitations to Inaugurations "M-W" 2001-2002 (Box-folder 20:7)
  - Invitations to Social Events 2001-2002 (Box-folder 21:1)
  - "Ja-Je" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 21:2)
  - "Jo-Ju" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 21:3)
  - Jefferson Memorial Foundation, Thomas - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 21:4)
  - Jefferson Scholars - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 21:5)
  - Joint Legislative Audit & Review Commission 2001-2002 (Box-folder 21:6)
  - "Ka-Ke" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 21:7)
  - "Kh-Ki" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 21:8)
  - "Kl-Kw" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 22:1)
  - "La-Le" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 22:2)
  - "Li" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 22:3)
  - "Lo-Ly" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 22:4)
  - Lacoste School of the Arts in France 2001 Sep.-Nov. (Box-folder 22:5)
  - Law - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 22:6)
  - Library - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 23:1)
  - "Ma" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 23:2)
  - "Mc-Me" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 23:3)
  - "Mh-Mi" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 23:4)
  - "Mo-My" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 23:5)
  - Management & Budget - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 23:6)
  - Mariners' Museum 2002 May-Jun. (Box-folder 24:1)
  - Mariners' Museum 2002 Jan.-Apr. (Box-folder 24:2)
  - Mariners' Museum 2001 Nov.-Dec. (Box-folder 24:3)
  - Mariners' Museum 2001 Oct. (Box-folder 24:4)
  - Mariners' Museum 2001 Jul.-Sep. (Box-folder 24:5)
  - Medical Center - General 2001-2002 (Box-folder 25:1)
  - Medical Center - Hospital 2001-2002 (Box-folder 25:2)
  - Medical Center - Medical School 2001-2002 (Box-folder 25:3)
  - Medical Center - Nursing School 2001-2002 (Box-folder 25:4)
  - Medical Center - Personnel 2001 Dec. (Box-folder 25:5)
  - Music - General 2001 Sep. (Box-folder 25:6)
  - "N-Nas" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 25:7)
  - "National A-National G" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 25:8)
  - "National I-National W" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 25:9)
  - "Nau-Ne" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 25:10)
  - "Ni-Ny" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 26:1)
  - National Association of State Universities & Land-Grant Colleges 2001-2002 (Box-folder 26:2)
  - National Science Foundation 2002 Jun. (Box-folder 26:3)
  - Nellie May Foundation 2001-2002 (Box-folder 26:4)
  - "O" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 26:5)
  - Oak Ridge Associated Universities 2001-2002 (Box-folder 26:6)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa 2001 Aug. (Box-folder 26:7)
  - "Pa" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 26:8)
  - "Pe-Ph" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 26:9)
  - "Pi-Pu" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 26:10)
  - Parking Garage 2002 May-Jun. (Box-folder 27:1)
  - Parking & Transportation (University) 2002 Apr.-May (Box-folder 27:2)
  - Physics - General 2001 Sep.-Oct. (Box-folder 27:3)
  - Planning - Virginia 2020 2000-2002 (Box-folder 27:4)
  - President's Cabinet 2001-2002 (Box-folder 27:5)
  - Procurement Services 2002 Mar. (Box-folder 27:6)
  - Provost 2002 Apr.-May (Box-folder 27:7)
  - Psychology 2002 Mar. (Box-folder 27:8)
  - "Q" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 27:9)
  - "Ra-Rh" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 27:10)
  - "Ric" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 27:11)
  - "Rid-Riv" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 27:12)
  - "Ro-Ry" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 28:1)
  - Recommendations "B-T" 2001-2002 (Box-folder 28:2)
  - Registrar 2001 Oct. (Box-folder 28:3)
  - Religious Studies 2002 Mar. (Box-folder 28:4)
  - Requests for Nominations "A-L" 2001-2002 (Box-folder 28:5)
  - Requests for Nominations "M-W" 2001-2002 (Box-folder 28:6)
  - Research & Public Service 2001-2002 (Box-folder 28:7)
  - ROTC - Air Force 2001 Oct. (Box-folder 28:8)
  - ROTC - Army 2001-2002 (Box-folder 28:9)
  - ROTC - Navy 2001 Jul.-Oct. (Box-folder 28:10)
  - "Sa-Sc" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 28:11)
  - "Se-Sl" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 28:12)
  - "Sm-Sn" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 29:1)
  - "Soc-Sos" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 29:2)
  - "Sou" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 29:3)
  - "Sp-Sta" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 29:4)
  - "Ste-Sy" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 29:5)
  - Sallie Mae - General 2002 May-Jun. (Box-folder 29:6)
  - Sallie Mae - General 2002 Jan.-Apr. (Box-folder 30:1)
  - Sallie Mae - General 2002 Jan. (Box-folder 30:2)
  - Sallie Mae - General 2001 Oct. (Box-folder 30:3)
  - Senate, Faculty - University 2001-2002 (Box-folder 30:4)
  - Southern Association of Colleges & Schools 2001-2002 (Box-folder 30:5)
  - Southern Regional Education Board 2002 Mar. (Box-folder 30:6)
  - Sponsored Programs 2001 Sep. (Box-folder 30:7)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia 2001 Oct.-2002 Jun. (Box-folder 30:8)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia 2001 Jul.-Sep. (Box-folder 31:1)
  - State Department of Education 2001-2002 (Box-folder 31:2)
  - Student Affairs 2002 Apr.-Jun. (Box-folder 31:3)
  - Student Affairs - Dean of Students Office 2002 Feb. (Box-folder 31:4)
  - Student Affairs - Fraternities & Sororities 2001-2002 (Box-folder 31:5)
  - Student Council 2001-2002 (Box-folder 31:6)
  - Summer Session 2001-2002 (Box-folder 31:7)
  - "Ta-Te" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 31:8)
  - "Th-To" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 31:9)
  - "Tr-Tw" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 31:10)
  - "U" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 32:1)
  - United States Department of Education 2002 Feb.-Jun. (Box-folder 32:2)
  - United States Department of Education 2001 Aug.-2002 Feb. (Box-folder 32:3)
  - United Way/Combined Charitable Campaign 2001-2002 (Box-folder 32:4)
  - University Research Association 2001-2002 (Box-folder 32:5)
  - University of Virginia College at Wise 2001-2002 (Box-folder 32:6)
  - University of Virginia Investment Management Company 2002 May-Jun. (Box-folder 32:7)
  - University of Virginia Investment Management Company 2002 Jan.-Apr. (Box-folder 33:1)
  - University of Virginia Investment Management Company 2001 Oct.-Dec. (Box-folder 33:2)
  - University of Virginia Investment Management Company 2001 Sep. (Box-folder 33:3)
  - University Police 2001 Sep.-Oct. (Box-folder 33:4)
  - University Press of Virginia 2001-2002 (Box-folder 33:5)
  - University Programs Council 2002 Apr.-May (Box-folder 33:6)
  - University Relations/News Office 2001-2002 (Box-folder 33:7)
  - "Va-Virginia B" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 33:8)
  - "Virginia C-Virginia F" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 34:1)
  - "Virginia G-Vr" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 34:2)
  - Virginia Business Higher Education Council 2001-2002 (Box-folder 34:3)
  - Virginia Festival of American Film 2001-2002 (Box-folder 34:4)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 2002 Apr.-May (Box-folder 34:5)
  - "Wa" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 34:6)
  - "We-Wi" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 34:7)
  - "Wo-Wy" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 34:8)
  - Women's Center 2001-2002 (Box-folder 35:1)
  - "Y" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 35:2)
  - "Z" Miscellaneous 2001-2002 (Box-folder 35:3)
- Series II: Seldom Used Permanent Files (Box 35-47)
  - Academic Plan 1992 Apr.-1993 Feb. (Box-folder 35:4)
  - Academic Plan 1991 Dec.-1992 Mar. (Box-folder 35:5)
  - Academic Plan 1991 Nov. (Box-folder 35:6)
  - Academic Plan 1991 Sept.-Oct. (Box-folder 35:7)
  - Athletics - NCAA Division I Board of Directors 1999 Jan.-Dec. (Box-folder 36:1)
  - Athletics - NCAA Division I Board of Directors 1998 Oct.-Dec. (Box-folder 36:2)
  - Athletics - NCAA Division I Board of Directors 1998 Sep. (Box-folder 36:3)
  - Athletics - NCAA Division I Board of Directors 1998 Jun.-Aug. (Box-folder 36:4)
  - Athletics - NCAA Division I Board of Directors 1998 Jan.-Apr. (Box-folder 36:5)
  - Board of Visitors - General 2001 Jun. (Box-folder 36:6)
  - Board of Visitors - General 2001 May (Box-folder 37:1)
  - Board of Visitors - General 2001 Apr. (Box-folder 37:2)
  - Board of Visitors - General 2001 Mar. (Box-folder 37:3)
  - Board of Visitors - General 2001 Jan.-Feb. (Box-folder 37:4)
  - Board of Visitors - General 2001 Jan. (Box-folder 37:5)
  - Board of Visitors - General 2000 Nov.-Dec. (Box-folder 37:6)
  - Board of Visitors - General 2000 Sep.-Oct. (Box-folder 37:7)
  - Board of Visitors - General 2000 Aug. (Box-folder 38:1)
  - Board of Visitors - General 2000 Jul. (Box-folder 38:2)
  - Board of Visitors - 1999-2000 Committees 1999 Apr. (Box-folder 38:3)
  - Board of Visitors - Academic Enhancement Program 1992 Oct.-1996 Mar. (Box-folder 38:4)
  - Board of Visitors - Academic Enhancement Program 1989 Sep.-1991 Sep. (Box-folder 38:5)
  - Board of Visitors - Ackerly, John P. III 2002 Aug.-2003 May (Box-folder 38:6)
  - Board of Visitors - Ackerly, John P. III 2002 Feb.-Jul. (Box-folder 38:7)
  - Board of Visitors - Ackerly, John P. III 2001 Jul.-2002 Jan. (Box-folder 38:8)
  - Board of Visitors - Ackerly, John P. III 2000 Sep..-2001 Jun. (Box-folder 38:9)
  - Board of Visitors - Ackerly, John P. III 1999 Nov.-2000 Aug. (Box-folder 39:1)
  - Board of Visitors - Ackerly, John P. III 1998 May-1999 Oct. (Box-folder 39:2)
  - Board of Visitors - Ackerly, John P. III 1996 Jun.-1998 Apr. (Box-folder 39:3)
  - Board of Visitors - Ackerly, John P. III 1996 Mar.-May (Box-folder 39:4)
  - Board of Visitors - Ackerly, John P. III 1995 Aug.-1996 Feb. (Box-folder 39:5)
  - Board of Visitors - Bliley, Thomas J. 2000 Mar.-2004 Jan. (Box-folder 39:6)
  - Board of Visitors - Caravati, Charles M. Jr 1994 Mar.-2000 Oct. (Box-folder 39:7)
  - Board of Visitors - Glazer, Charles L. 2000 Mar.-2003 Mar. (Box-folder 39:8)
  - Board of Visitors - Greer, T. Keister 1995 Mar.-2003 Jan. (Box-folder 39:9)
  - Board of Visitors - Holland, Elsie Goodwyn 1994 Mar.-2000 May (Box-folder 39:10)
  - Board of Visitors - Robertson, Timothy B. 1998 Mar.-2001 Oct. (Box-folder 39:11)
  - Board of Visitors - Standing Committees 1981 Jun.-2000 May (Box-folder 39:12)
  - Board of Visitors - Twohy, Elizabeth A. 1995 Mar.-2003 Jan. (Box-folder 40:1)
  - Walker, Walter F. "Wally" 1997 Jan.-2000 Nov. (Box-folder 40:2)
  - Board of Visitors - Wheat, James C. III 1997 Mar.-2001 Mar. (Box-folder 40:3)
  - Board of Visitors - Wolfe, Joseph E. 1998 Mar.-2000 Oct. (Box-folder 40:4)
  - Center for Advanced Studies - General 1993 Jan.-1997 Mar. (Box-folder 40:5)
  - Center for Advanced Studies - General 1991 Jul.-1992 Sep. (Box-folder 40:6)
  - Center for Advanced Studies - Advisory Board 1994 Apr.-Nov. (Box-folder 40:7)
  - Center for Advanced Studies - Advisory Board 1992 Sep.-1993 Sep. (Box-folder 40:8)
  - Center for Advanced Studies - Advisory Board 1991 Sep.-1992 Mar. (Box-folder 40:9)
  - Center for Advanced Studies - Membership in Center 1992 Apr.-Aug. (Box-folder 40:10)
  - Center for Advanced Studies - Visiting Committee: International Programs 1986 Jan. (Box-folder 40:11)
  - Center for Advanced Studies - Visiting Committee: Psychology Department 1987 Apr. (Box-folder 40:12)
  - Development - Capital Campaign 1997 Dec.-1998 Nov. (Box-folder 41:1)
  - Development - Capital Campaign 1997 Jun. (Box-folder 41:2)
  - Development - Capital Campaign 1996 Nov.-1997 Apr. (Box-folder 41:3)
  - Development - Capital Campaign 1996 Jul.-Sep. (Box-folder 41:4)
  - Development - Campaign Council 1994 Jun.-1995 Apr. (Box-folder 41:5)
  - Development - Executive Committee - Campaign 2001 Apr.-May. (Box-folder 41:6)
  - Development - Executive Committee - Campaign 2000 Aug.-2001. Jan (Box-folder 41:7)
  - Development - Executive Committee - Campaign 1999 Dec.-2000 Jun. (Box-folder 41:8)
  - Development - Executive Committee - Campaign 1998 Nov.-1999 Aug. (Box-folder 42:1)
  - Development - Executive Committee - Campaign 1997 Oct.-1998 Sep. (Box-folder 42:2)
  - Development - Executive Committee - Campaign 1997 Mar.-Jun. (Box-folder 42:3)
  - Development - Executive Committee - Campaign 1995 Sep.-1997 Jan. (Box-folder 42:4)
  - Development - Major Gift Initiatives 1993-1995 (Box-folder 42:5)
  - Development - National Leadership Gifts Council 1996 (Box-folder 42:6)